# Shakib Quraishy

Bangladesh



quraishyshakib@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/shakibquraishy

# Summary

Being a Human Resources Professional, I am developing and preparing myself every day to be competent enough to deal with all the activities of the Human Resources Department, starting from recruitment & selection to training & development, performance appraisal, compensation & benefit and HR operations. Not to be a specialist only in one segment but to be a performer of all the HR activities is my ultimate goal.

## **Experience**



## **Human Resources Executive**

### Notionhive

Oct 2021 - Present (9 months +)

- 1. Recruitment & Selection.
- 2. Employee onboarding.
- 3. Leave Management.
- 4. Working on improving organizational culture.
- 5. Working on team building activities.
- 6. Maintaining & updating employee database on a regular basis.
- 7. Conducting exit interviews & ensuring smooth employee offboarding.
- 8. Working on different aspects of organizational development.
- 9. Ensuring KPI based performance appraisal across the departments.
- 10. Assisting the Finance department in preparing monthly salary sheets.
- 11. Performing different activities of HR operations.

## **Executive-HR & Administration**

Pro Adman

Jan 2021 - Sep 2021 (9 months)

# Human Resources Executive

Omicon Group

Oct 2019 - Aug 2020 (11 months)

- 1. Recruitment & Selection.
- 2. Employee Joining.
- 3. Policy & SOP Development.
- 4. Developing Department-Wise Job Description & Job Specification.
- 5. Preparing Proposals, Promotion Letter, Transfer Letter, Show-Cause Letter, Office Orders & other Official Letters.
- 6. Leave Management.

### Human Resources Intern

SSG (Super Star Group)

Feb 2019 - Jun 2019 (5 months)

- 1. Managing Id card & business card of the employees.
- 2. Maintaining the personal files of the employees.
- 3. Assisting in maintaining employee attendance record.
- 4. Accepting Resign letters & doing smooth settlement of the resignee.
- 5. Conducting interviews & taking exams.
- 6. Updating & maintaining the employee personal file database.
- 7. Preparing salary deduction report to support the payroll process.
- 8. Contacting the candidates for interviews or for any other issues.
- 9. Supporting in the employee confirmation process.

## **Education**



# United International University

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Human Resources Management/ Personnel Administration, General 2014 - 2018

## **Skills**

Microsoft Word • Microsoft Excel • HR Policies • Cross-cultural Communication Skills • Fluency in English